<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on John&#39;s Tech Logs - Discover Issues, Share Solutions.</title>
    <link>https://johnstechlogs.com/en/categories/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on John&#39;s Tech Logs - Discover Issues, Share Solutions.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:49:12 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://johnstechlogs.com/en/categories/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building my First Mini ITX PC</title>
      <link>https://johnstechlogs.com/en/building-my-first-mini-itx-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 03:49:12 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnstechlogs.com/en/building-my-first-mini-itx-pc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-a-pc&#34;&gt;Building a PC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I never completely built a PC by myself. I knew building your own was cheaper than buying prebuilts. In 2020, I wanted to move away from using an external GPU dock for my laptop to a desktop. I had a lot of fun picking out the parts for my new system. When it came to building it, people always said it was like building legos and I loved legos. However, I am not the best when it comes to hardware or cable management. I had a friend come over and help me build my desktop. Unfortunately, he took over most of the process and I felt like I missed out. The build was a success and it&amp;rsquo;s lasted me five years. Now that I have a solid income, I think it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://johnstechlogs.com/images/miniitxpc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kodak Ektar H35 - The Best Beginners Film Camera</title>
      <link>https://johnstechlogs.com/en/kodak-ektar-h35---the-best-beginners-film-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 03:49:12 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnstechlogs.com/en/kodak-ektar-h35---the-best-beginners-film-camera/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-best-beginners-film-camera&#34;&gt;The Best Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Film Camera&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve probably seen those vintage and grainy looking photos on social media. You can replicate that with any old filter but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel authentic since it was digitally crafted. Film is simply thin strips that store images after being exposed to light. I was chasing the authenticity. My first experience with film cameras was using a disposable kodak camera. It was fun using a point and shoot and anticipating how it would come out after I went to get it developed. I feel that film photos really shine when people are just being themselves and having fun. Of course the disposable had no use once the roll was out. Then I came across the Kodak Ektar 35. This was a reusable film camera from Kodak. This meant I could get the same point and shoot feeling, keep the camera, and reuse it by refilling the rolls. I loved the way the body looked with its vintage aesthetic. I&amp;rsquo;ve received compliments about it in public.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of the Backfire G2 Black Electric Skateboard</title>
      <link>https://johnstechlogs.com/en/a-review-of-the-backfire-g2-black-electric-skateboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 03:49:12 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnstechlogs.com/en/a-review-of-the-backfire-g2-black-electric-skateboard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;electric-skating-as-a-beginner-skater&#34;&gt;Electric Skating as a Beginner Skater&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have never properly skated on a normal skateboard. My body won&amp;rsquo;t let me attempt dangerous things where I am not in complete control. That&amp;rsquo;s where the electric board controller comes in. With this controller, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to know the exact speed I am moving at and more importantly, stop when I have to. The only thing I would have to worry about is balance and turning. On the contrary, most skaters would just recommend getting a normal board so you can build confidence, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t entirely my goal to be a real skater. I did my research and found an entry level electric board that wasn&amp;rsquo;t too pricey and didn&amp;rsquo;t have all the fancy features. I opted for the Backfire G2 Black since it was on sale and looked sleek while being aimed at beginners.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
